# Rodrigo Antonio Guzmán Castro

Phone: +56-9-50503351– email: <a href="mailto:rodrigoguzman1202@gmail.com">rodrigoguzman1202@gmail.com</a> <a href="mailto:https://www.linkedin.com/in/rodrigo-guzman-a5277115b/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/rodrigo-guzman-a5277115b/</a>

Portfolio: https://lkaza.github.io/

## **Professional Profile**

Technical Artist with 2 years of experience in Unity3D, mostly in charge of importing characters and 3D models into Unity and creating different effects using Shaderlab with URP to improve the visual performance.

Over my career I've been working with artists to ensure the art looks the way they want to. I've learned Blender software to understand the creative process behind 3D Stylized characters.

### **Technical Skills**

Programming Languages:

- 2 years of C#.
- 1 year of **ShaderLab**.
- 2 years Relational databases **SQL**.
- lava
- Javascript.
- MongoDB.
- NodeJS.

#### Experience in:

- Agile methodology Scrum and Kanban.
- Particle System in Unity.
- VFX Graph.
- Amplify Shader Editor/Shader Graph.
- Repositories Git/Github.
- Adobe Photoshop.
- Generalist 3D Blender.
  PolyModelling,UV Map,Textures,Rigging.

# **Employment**

## **Imaginima**

April 2022 - Present

#### **Technical Artist and VFX Artist.**

- Ensured performance using Baked Illumination and Occlusion Culling.
- Developed UI and backend for an Inventory System capable of being used with navigation using the new input system.
- Established work pipeline for 3D characters.
- Developed shaders for particles, textures, noises and some 3D with rigging and animations.

## **YPF**

June 2019 - December 2019

#### **Network Administrator (TI)**

- Managed connections of users in integrated Enterprise systems.
- Set up new devices and helped new employees of YPF with their new devices (Phones-Tablets-Laptops).
- Made weekly reports to managers to ensure meeting deadlines.

# **Personal Projects**

#### Rem

October 2021 - December 2021

### Generalist 3D Artist and Unity Developer

- Made a 3D model from scratch to rig/texture in blender.
- Used the Magica Cloth asset from the unity store for physics management
- Experimented with many toon shaders, but decided to use Unity Chan to achieve a clean toon anime character.

### KeloWar

June 2021

# **Unity Developer**

- Made a technical prototype of Android development.
- Replicated core game mechanics of android game "Archero".

### Headworld

January 2021- February-2021

### **Unity Graphics Programmer**

- Received network package and reflect animations for characters.
- Implemented a day and night system in Unity.
- Deactivated objects far from the player.
- Developed shaders like a water fountain, lava, and other environmental assets.
- Imported 3D characters to Unity and developed an animation system for blending between them.

# **PyroBoom**

July-2020

### **Unity Developer**

- Made a procedural map for endless survival.
- Animated through code using C#.

#### Education

2013-2019

Engineering Informatics Bachelor's Degree – Universidad de Playa Ancha

## **Seminaries and Courses**

| October 2021 | Making A Stylized Toon Shadering Within Unity - Wingfox              |
|--------------|--|
| June 2020    | Math For Video Games: The Fastest Way To Get Smarter At Math - Udemy |
| May 2020     | RPG Core Combat Creator: Learn Intermediate Unity C# Coding – Udemy  |
| March 2020   | Complete C# Unity Game Developer 3D - Udemy                          |